https://www.cama.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
CAMA respects your right to privacy. This policy summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your privacy.
Information Collection
CAMA will only collect personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through our Internet site or e-mail correspondence. We will collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information) to improve our Internet site and better meet your needs.
Use of Information
Before we collect any personally identifiable information, we will provide an explanation for the possible use of your data. The information you supply will be used by CAMA to respond to your request. Authorized third parties may be utilized by CAMA to collect, track and process such information. If you have submitted personal information to CAMA electronically and would like it removed or modified, please contact us. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request.
Security
CAMA does not sell, lease, or distribute publicly personally identifiable information.
Other Important Information
The CAMA Internet site may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites.
It may be necessary, if required by law or if pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personally identifiable information.
CAMA reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications on this page.
